[
    { "question": "はい", "pronunciation": "hai", "answer": "Yes", "language" : "jap" },
    { "question": "いいえ", "pronunciation": "iie", "answer": "No" , "language" : "jap"},
    { "question": "おねがい　します", "pronunciation": "onegai shimasu", "answer": "Please" , "language" : "jap"},
    { "question": "こんにちわ", "pronunciation": "konnichiwa", "answer": "Hello" , "language" : "jap"},
    { "question": "はじめまして", "pronunciation": "hajimemashite", "answer": "Nice to meet you", "language" : "jap" },
    { "question": "もしもし", "pronunciation": "moshi moshi", "answer": "Hello" , "language" : "jap"},
    { "question": "すみません", "pronunciation": "sumimasen", "answer": "Excuse me", "language" : "jap" },
    { "question": "ありがとう", "pronunciation": "Arigatō", "answer": "Thank you", "language" : "jap" },
    { "question": "ごめんなさい", "pronunciation": "gomenasai", "answer": "Sorry" , "language" : "jap"},
    
    {"question": "안녕하세요", "pronunciation": "Ahnyunghaseyo", "answer": "Hello", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "어떻게 지내세요", "pronunciation": "Uhduhkeh jinehseyo", "answer": "How are you", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "감사합니다", "pronunciation": "Kamsahanida", "answer": "Thank you", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "알았어", "pronunciation": "Arasseo", "answer": "Ok", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "역시", "pronunciation": "Yeoksi", "answer": "Also", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "잠시만요", "pronunciation": "Jamshimanyo", "answer": "Excuse me", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "주세요", "pronunciation": "Juseyo", "answer": "Please", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "최성합니다", "pronunciation": "Chwayseonghamnida", "answer": "Sorry", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "사랑해", "pronunciation": "Saranghae", "answer": "I love you", "language": "kor"},
    {"question": "반갑습니다", "pronunciation": "Bangapsumnida", "answer": "Nice to meet you", "language": "kor"},
    
    {"question": "Muchas Gracías", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Thank you", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Felicidades", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Congrats", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Hasta Mañana", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "See you tomorrow", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Amigo", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Friend", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Hola", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Hello", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Viva La Vida", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Long live life", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Adiós", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Goodbye", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Lo siento", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Sorry", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Por favor", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Please", "language": "spa"},
    {"question": "Me gusta", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "I like", "language": "spa"},
    
    {"question": "你好", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Hello", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "谢谢", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Thank you", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "狗", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Dog", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "是", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Yes", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "爱", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Love", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "早安", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Good morning", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "朋友", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Friend", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "我们", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "We", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "好吃", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Delicious", "language": "chi"},
    {"question": "对不起", "pronunciation": "", "answer": "Sorry", "language": "chi"}
]
